wiggle.com.au 2014-07-02

# Wiggle Customer Services

**Wiggle Ltd**  are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and secondly to provide you with the best service possible. We will not email you in the future unless you have given us your consent. We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us in the future.

**Contact information:**

Wiggle Ltd  
3 Optima  
Northarbour Spur  
Portsmouth  
Hampshire  
PO6 3TU  
United Kingdom

Email: [Contact Us](http://www.wiggle.com.au/ContactUsForm)

Executive Directors: Stefan Barden

**Information:**

The type of information we will collect about you when you place an order or register on our web site includes:

  * Address
  * Phone Number
  * Email Address

This information is stored on our internal systems and our website simply verifies you as a customer of Wiggle. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by visiting your account or emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly. The personal information that we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. We will not transfer or sell your information. We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should email us at [info@wiggle.com.au](mailto:info@wiggle.com.au).

We use the information you provide for the following purposes:

  * Aid strategic development
  * Audit usage of the site

**Use of personal information**

We process personal information collected via Wiggle for the purpose of:  

  * providing the best possible service processing any orders you may have made
  * providing you with information about products and services we offer

When you place an order we need to know your name, email address, delivery address and payment information, depending on the payment method that you choose to use. This allows us to process and fulfil your order and to notify you of the status of your request. We may also ask for your telephone number which enables us to contact you urgently if there is a problem with your order.

**Newsletter Subscription**

Your e-mail address will be used for our own marketing purposes until you unsubscribe. It is possible to unsubscribe at any time. If you do not wish to receive information about our products or services you can unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscribe link, which exists at the top of all marketing emails sent by Wiggle, or by managing your subscription status in your account pages on the Wiggle website.

**Your Consent**  
By submitting information to Wiggle you consent to the collection and use of this information by Wiggle and its Service Provider (if any) in the fullfilment of your order. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Data Security**  
We have designed our site to protect the information we collect online from unauthorised access. We safeguard your private information by implementing the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedure necessary to protect your privacy. To further protect your security, we also take the reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to your personal profile or making data changes. We are committed to protecting your privacy and have security measures in place to prevent unauthorised access to and disclosure of your personal information.

**Improving Our Service**  
Wiggle does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. To better tailor our services to our customers' needs, we use non-identifying and aggregate information to help us make decisions on how to improve Wiggle. We also share this generic information with our advertisers and other interested, reputable parties with whom we have established a formal business relationship. For example, we may tell advertisers which areas of the site have received the most customer traffic overall, or more specifically, how many customer types have visited certain pages. However, we do not disclose the identifying information of individual customers with advertisers. We also do not use or share the personally identifiable information submitted to us by any other means without providing our customers the choice to opt-out or otherwise bar such unrelated uses.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's (or alternative web browsing device’s) hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognise your browser and to provide rich shopping features such as recommend products and loyalty discounts, as well as the storage of items in your Shopping Basket between visits. The Help menu in most common browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Wiggle’s essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Wiggle.co.uk features that require you to Sign in. If you do leave cookies turned on, be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

Please read our  **full** [Cookie Policy](http://www.wiggle.com.au/h/option/Cookies) for further information.

**Analytic Tools**

  * Google Analytics is a system used by many website to record information about visits to their website. Google set six different cookies with expiry dates ranging from 30 minutes to 2 years. These cookies are used mainly to differentiate between first time visitors to a website and repeat visitors. They also allow us to ensure our website performs as well as possible for our users. The cookies are able to collect an anonymous customer number when a user is logged into the website, allowing our backend systems to ensure accuracy of Google Analytics data and help us ensure your website experience remains relevant across devices. They do not contain any personally identifiable information. You can find out more about how Google use cookies at http://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ (English only)
  * Please read our  **full** [Cookie Policy](http://www.wiggle.com.au/h/option/Cookies) for further information.
  * Wiggle may from time to time share your details with third party analytical resources for the purposes of better understanding customer behaviour and performance, website performance, improved ad relevance and any other analytical process to give Wiggle a better understanding of how to develop its offering to its customers. These third parties will be employed solely for the purpose of the aforementioned analytical purposes, and as such Wiggle will ensure that the third party is contractually obliged to use the data only for the analytical purposes set out in the agreement between Wiggle and the third party, and Wiggle will also ensure that the third party is contractually required to maintain a level of security around the shared data, at least as safe as Wiggle itself employs. Failure on the part of the third party to meet its contractual obligations will result in Wiggle recovering the data, and taking all reasonable actions to ensure the third party no longer has access to the shared data. Any third party cookies used on Wiggle will adhere to the same standards as first party cookies and not collect any personally identifiable information.

**Social Media Plug-ins**  
Social Media Plug-ins for Facebook and Twitter obtain data for tracking purposes.

**International Privacy**  
The above privacy statement may not be applicable in all countries of Wiggle visitors or registered community users, as security policies may vary according to the individual Internet laws in each host country.

**Disclosures**

We will not pass your information to any third parties. You can also email us to stop receiving any information about us and our services by clicking [here](mailto:info@wiggle.com.au). If you have any queries about our Privacy Statement you should contact us by e-mail [data@wiggle.co.uk](mailto:data@wiggle.co.uk).

(back to top)

* * *

Wiggle maintains a strict privacy policy in full accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

We expect you to maintain the confidentiality of your username and password for your Wiggle account.

We will never sell or pass on your name and address to any other organisation without your consent. Your details are confidential and you will never receive unsolicited mail as a result of ordering from Wiggle.

Unless otherwise stated, all rights, including copyright, in the content, text and graphics of these Wiggle web pages are owned and controlled for these purposes by Wiggle Ltd. You are not permitted to copy, broadcast, download, store, transmit, show or play in public, adapt or change in any way the content of these Wiggle pages for any other purpose whatsoever, in any medium, without the prior written permission of Wiggle Ltd.

In accessing Wiggle web pages, you agree that you may only download the content for your own individual and non-commercial use.

(back to top)

* * *

Feel free to use small quotes as long as you acknowledge our site and provide a link back to the original source.

(back to top)

* * *

**jQuery - JavaScript Library**  
jQuery JavaScript Library v1.7.1  

**Copyright 2012, John Resig**  
Dual licensed under the MIT or GPL Version 2 licenses.  
<http://jquery.org/license>

**Includes Sizzle.js**  
Copyright 2011, The Dojo Foundation  
Released under the MIT, BSD, and GPL Licenses.

**Image Toolset - 360 Spin and Zoom**  
Image Toolset 360 Spin and Zoom v1.0.0  
The 360 Spin and Zoom is Copyright of Image Toolset Ltd - © Image Toolset Ltd. 2012. All rights reserved.  
Any inclusion, redistribution, modification, resell or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited.  
You may not, except with Image Toolset Ltd.’s express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content.  
Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.

**hoverIntent**  
hoverIntent v6  
hoverIntent is currently available for use in all personal or commercial projects under both MIT and GPL licenses.  
This means that you can choose the license that best suits your project, and use it accordingly.

**imagesLoaded**  
jQuery imagesLoaded plugin v2.0.1  
<http://github.com/desandro/imagesloaded>  
MIT License. by Paul Irish et al.

**iosSlider**  
http://iosscripts.com/iosslider/  
Copyright (c) 2012 Marc Whitbread  
iosSlider is licensed under the Creative Commons – Attribution-NonCommercial 3.0 License.

**jCarouselLite**  
jCarouselLite - jQuery plugin to navigate images/any content in a carousel style widget.  
Copyright (c) 2012 Ganeshji Marwaha (gmarwaha.com)  
Dual licensed under the MIT and GPL licenses:  
<http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php>  
<http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html>  
Version: 1.0.1

**jQzoom Evolution Library**  
jQzoom Evolution Library v2.3 - Javascript Image magnifier  
Copyright 2012, Engineer Marco Renzi  
Licensed under the BSD license.  
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:  
Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.  
Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.  
Neither the name of the organization nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.  
Date: 03 May 2011 22:16:00

**jquery.thslide.js**  
jquery.thslide.js  
v.0.1  
Julien Decaudin - 04/2010  

**jQuery UI**  
jQuery UI 1.8.17  
jQuery UI Widget 1.8.17  
jQuery UI Mouse 1.8.17  
jQuery UI Position 1.8.17  
jQuery UI Dialog 1.8.17  
jQuery UI Slider 1.8.17  
Copyright 2011, AUTHORS.txt <http://jqueryui.com/about>  
Dual licensed under the MIT or GPL Version 2 licenses.  
<http://jquery.org/license>

**Unobtrusive-Ajax**  
Unobtrusive Ajax support library for jQuery  
Copyright (C) Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.

**Zebra_TransForm**  
<http://stefangabos.ro/>  
author Stefan Gabos   
version 2.0.1 (last revision: August 07, 2011)  
copyright (c) 2011 Stefan Gabos  
license <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl-3.0.txt> GNU LESSER GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE  
package Zebra_TransForm

(back to top)

* * *
